After that, we can turn on the other parts and hide them and prevent them from participating in the simulation.
Then we can start to make the wrapping material of the sofa pad.
First, use the basic length measurement tool to measure the length by clicking on the outside of the electronic model.
The side can also be measured. Click on one point first, then move to another point, double-click to complete the creation.
Use the editing measurement virtual model tool to select the measurement line to check the total length.
Then create a rectangular sheet according to the measurement value, which is slightly larger than the measurement size.
Click on the positioning function in the upper right corner of the positioning ball to position the sheet to the sofa pad.
Then use the positioning ball to move the sheet to the top of the sofa pad.
After moving, you can manually adjust the size to roughly cover the entire sofa pad.
For the front edge of the sofa pad, for the back edge of the sofa pad, you can adjust the position by pressing the button in the right-duty and press the button in the left-duty.
There are 2 options for you to choose, to choose the side edge by pressing the button in the left-duty.
Then we will make the side edge.
You can create a rectangle as a side edge according to the measurement method.
You can also create a rectangular sheet as a side edge.
Then we can take the middle of the side edge and poke a hole on it and do a circle.
Select a circle with the tool and you can see the total length of these lines
Then create a total length x height of the plate
Then create a joint plate, so that the two rectangular plates can be edited at the same time
Switch to the physical surface to see the opposite side
After arranging the position, because the bottom plate is now facing the back, so turn the plate over on the surface to ensure that the front is facing the back
Choose the free sewing tool, click on the side of the long strip plate first, then create a sewing line along the side, double-click to complete the first half
Then go to the rectangular plate, click along the side, determine the direction of the seam, ensure that the front is facing the outside, double-click to complete the creation
The bottom is the same, if you encounter an invisible position, you can change the perspective, continue to click, and double-click to complete the creation
After adding to the side, the sewing line will arrange the rectangular plate on the sides of the two plates
After opening the simulation, because there are more model faces, there may be a problem of penetration, so drag it
Divide the line on the side as well
The model face will be more visible, and the pattern will be more visible
Now reduce the vertical and horizontal distance between the plate and the model, so that the mesh will be more visible, so that the mesh will not interfere with the model
Then reduce the thickness of the collision to shorten the distance between the plate and the model
Now close the door and close the door
Select the outer layer and create an outer layer on the outer side of the dragon layer to create a fold to make the seat position.
Remove the sewing line created by the dragon layer, because now the sewing line is a whole circle, so that the excess part will be spread evenly on the four edges.
Therefore, we have to sew one by one separately.
After sewing, change the type of sewing line to Turned, so that the sewing edge is more even.
Then change the fabric to the top, which is convenient to do some special effects later.
Apply pressure 5 to the outer layer of the board to make it inflatable.
Then apply pressure 5 to the outer layer of the board to make it inflatable.
Because of the current Stitchablites connection, if you change the outer layer, the inner layer will also change at the same time.
Therefore, it will be modified after the Stitchablites challenged is finished.
Because of the communion relationship, the inner layer also changes at the same time, if the outer layer is modified, the inner layer will also change at the same time.
Since the 10,000-layer plate is relatively large, applying the correct pressure will create the effect of
If you feel that the pressure is too obvious at 5, you can also change the pressure to 3 or lower.
Now we return the pressure to 5 to make some pleating details
Double-clamp frame center, the center of the plate is the point of contact, widen the plate
Change the fabric to the usual leather fabric
The bending strength is very good
If the bending strength is too high, the pleating details will be lost
It can reduce the bending strength of the golden tail and greatly reduce the bending strength of the right foot line
This can generate more detailed pleating
Adjusting the tension of the right foot line can maintain the pleating at the seam side while creating more or less pleating in the right foot line direction
If the strength of the 산
So in the direction of Jin Sha, the fabric will get easier to stretch, and will spread more due to the pressure
The width of the skirt sunrise andörper
On the contrary, if theridge is larger, the fabric will not stretch easily in the direction of Jin Sha
Can move to the side lens to see the effect
The spin Кan change dress Nigayan曲鏡頭看一下效果
Because the outer plate is stretched a lot along the tail, so we can focus on the strength of the tail.
When the tail strength is high, there will be a lot of hard wrinkles on the tail, and if you turn it over, the wrinkles will disappear.
Can be adjusted according to the need to compare the effect
Reduce the particle strength to 5, you can see that there are more wrinkle details.
If you feel that the wrinkle is not enough, you can increase the strength of the tail.
Show all models
Пом
Rotate the model, lower the surface tightness to prevent the air around the model from being reduced and affecting the fabric.
forward